Like I say, welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
where we open up with the ten
commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep. Brother Tanzel,
and God spake all these words, saying,
>> I am the Lord thy God, which hath
brought thee out of the land of Egypt,
out of the house of bondage. Thou shall
have no other gods before me. Thou shall
not make unto the eating grave in image,
or any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above, or that is in the earth
beneath, or that is in the water under
the earth. Thou shall not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. Why the
Lord thy God am a jealous God, visiting
the iniquities of the fathers upon the
children, unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me, and
showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in [clears throat] vain, for the
Lord will not hold him guilt that take
up his name in vain. Remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy. Six days sh
thy labor do all thy work, but the
seventh day is the Sabbath of the Lord
thy God. In it thou shall not do any
work. Thou nor thy son, nor thy
daughter, thy man's servant, nor thy
maid servant, nor thy cattle, and nor
thy stranger that is within thy gates.
For in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea, and all that in the
midst, and rested the seventh day. But
for the Lord blessed the Sabbath day,
and hollowed it. Honor thy father and
thy mother,
>> that thy days may be long upon the land
which the Lord thy God giveth thee. Thou
shall not kill. Thou shall not commit
adultery. Thou shall not steal. Thou
shall not bear false witness against thy
neighbor. Thou shall not cover the
neighbor's house. Thou not covered the
neighbor's wife, nor his man's servant,
nor his maid servant, nor his ox, nor
his ass, nor anything that is neighbors.
We read Exodus 21-17. And may the Lord
have a blessing to the reading of his
words. In Jesus name we pray. Amen.
>> Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time. The questions we
will not answer are the vague and the
long scripture questions as well as
questions of debate. We are not here to
debate. We are here to spread the true
gospel of Jesus. So please be as direct
as possible with your questions so we
can be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible. No
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program. Also keep
in mind that this is a live stream. So
feel free to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life. We just
asking that you keep them to a two
scripture maximum. But let me introduce
to you the family that's on the panel
this evening. We got brother Dre.
>> Good evening, brother Jerome.
>> Raise in peace.
>> Brother Julius.
>> Good evening everybody.
>> Brother Tenzel.
>> Good evening everyone. Sister Deborah,
>> good evening.
>> And we have Sister Casey with us as well
as the guest caller. And I'm brother
Cornell. Sister Deborah, before we get
to our first question of the evening, I
just wanted to send this quick shout out
to Skyrider 53 that we appreciate your
zeal and your desire to have your
questions answered, but we're setting a
standard tonight that we would not
answer more than two questions from one
individual.
So, Sister Deborah, now we can begin
with our first question of the evening.
Uh yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A. Uh
Orlando Davyy asks, "Should we observe
Hanukkah and John 10:es 22 and 23 are
given?"
>> John 10:es 22 and 23. Brother Julius,
what about observing Hanatha?
Uh let's let's go to that John 10.
Let's go to John 10. Hanukkah
uh also called the festival of lights or
feast of lights uh supposedly uh the
rededication of the of the temple in
Jerusalem.
And the question is should we observe
Hanekah?
Let's see what the book calls this
according to the scripture that they
gave. when you get it. TZ John 10:22 and
23. Go ahead.
>> And it was at Jerusalem, the feast of
the dedication, and it was winter, and
Jesus walked in the temple in Solomon's
porch.
>> What can we add to that?
It said
it was Jerusalem.
It was a feast of dedication.
And it was winter. And Jesus walked in
Solomon's porch.
We can't add to it. We can't take away
from it. It read what it read. Now let's
go to Leviticus the 23rd chapter.
Leviticus 23 read 1 and 2. Tanzil.
And the Lord spake unto Moses, saying,
"Speak unto the children of Israel, and
say unto them, concerning the feast of
the Lord, which ye shall proclaim
>> concerning what?
>> The feast of the Lord."
>> Okay, go ahead.
>> Which ye shall proclaim to be holy
convocation.
>> And God calls them holy convocations.
And what else?
>> Even these are my feast.
>> Verse four,
>> these are the feasts of the Lord. Even
>> feast of the Lord,
>> even holy convocation
we should which ye shall proclaim in
their season.
>> From there, sisters and brothers, on
your own, read the whole chapter and see
if you could if the feast of dedication
is called the feast of the Lord,
>> right?
>> It's not there.
And if you want to find out more about
the dedication, you can read on your
own. You could read um Nehemiah, what is
it? Nehemiah the 12th chapter, but none
of that is in the feast of the Lord.
That's a civil feast that they had. So,
should we keep dedication? We at the
Hanukkah, we at the Israel of God keep
the feast of the Lord. That's all I got.
>> All right. Hope that answers your
question. As we move on to our next one,
>> moving on. Skyrider says, "Can you show
scripture that indicates that the false
prophet actually outranks the beast?"
>> All right. Does the false prophet
actually outrank the beast, Brother
Jerome?
>> Yeah, we can we can show some verses um
that show that. Let's let's go to uh
Revelations chapter 17 and we're going
to read verse 1-4.
Revelation 17:es 1-4. When you get it,
go ahead and read.
>> And there came one of the seven angels,
which had the seven vows, and talk with
me, saying unto me, come hither. and I
will show unto thee the judgment of the
great that siteth upon many waters
with whom the kings of the earth have
committed fornication and the
inhabitants of the earth has been made
drunk with the wine of her fornication.
So he carried me away in the spirit into
the wilderness. And I saw a woman sit
upon a scarlet- colored beast full of
names of blasphemy, having seven heads
and 10 horns. And the woman was arrayed
in purple and scarlet color and decked
with gold and precious stones and
pearls, having a golden cup in her hand
full of abomination and filthiness of
her fornication.
>> So I I just want to establish who this
this woman is. this this woman is the
false prophet that you mentioned in in
your question uh and uh he's the pope
the pope of Rome or Vatican City and the
beast that we read about you know
there's a there's a beast who is a
political leader
uh of the beast with the seven heads and
10 horns that's [snorts] the beast too
okay uh and they both had to sign the
treaties of Rome and have a they had to
sign a treaty called the treaties of
Rome because of the pope in Rome who is
riding this scarlet colored beast with
the seven heads and 10 horns. Okay. So
he's he he he he's ranking over him.
That's why he's sitting on on this
scarlet color beast. Okay. Uh now if you
go to uh Google Google search and type
in uh who signed the treaties of Rome
uh it'll it'll pull up that the treaties
of Rome was was signed by the European
Union over there in Western Europe.
Okay.
And we still talking about the beast
with seven heads and 10 horns. Okay. Uh
one more verse. Can you read verse 18
and that'll be it?
And the woman which thou sawest is that
great city which reignth reignth over
the kings of the earth.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's it. That's all I got.
>> That great city is Vatican City, right,
brother?
>> Yes, it is.
>> All right. Thank you very much for that.
Hope that answered their question as we
move
move on to our next
>> moving on. Uh, Jennifer Love says, "If a
person makes a vow without knowing the
true word of God and is not baptized,
are they accountable for the vow?"
>> All right. So, um, if you make a vow and
you know a true word and you wasn't
baptized, are you accountable for the
vow? Guest caller.
Okay, let's go with let's let's go and
read a couple of things. Let's go to
Leviticus 5th chapter. We're going to
read verses 2 through 5.
Leviticus 5
and read
>> 2 through five.
>> Okay.
Or if a soul touch any unclean thing,
whether it be of a carcass of an unclean
beast, or a carcass of unclean cattle,
or the carcass of unclean creeping
things, and if it be hidden from him, he
also shall be unclean and guilty. Or if
he touch the uncleanness of a man,
whatsoever uncleanness it be that a man
shall be defiled with all, and if he hid
from him when he knoweth of it, then he
shall be guilty. Or if a soul swear
pronouncing with his lips to do evil or
to do good, whatsoever it be that a man
shall pronounce with an oath, and it be
hid from him, when he knoweth of it,
then he shall be guilty in one of these.
And it shall be when he shall be guilty
in one of these things, he shall confess
that he hath sinned in that thing.
>> Now, what verse was that? That was in a
fivey.
>> No. So the whole thing is if you do
anything I just use that because as an
example anything and you're not aware of
it you are guilty but once you find out
about it then you have to uh uh uh well
you have to make uh uh go to the priest
and he make an atonement for through
animal sacrifice. But being that the uh
animal sacrifices have been replaced,
once you find out that you've done
[clears throat] something,
then uh when you find the truth out
about it, then you have to go and make
an atonement. And this way, what you do
is you uh uh repent
and ask the Lord forgive you if you're
offended. And then you go and get
baptized.
That's that's because uh you was
unaware. That's why I said that it was
hid from you. Give you another example.
Let's see what Jesus said to some
Pharisees here. Let's go to St. John the
9th chapter.
We're going to read verse 39 to 41.
John 9:39-41
and Jesus said, "For judgment I am come
into this world, that they might which
see not might see, and that they which
might see be made blind." And some of
the Pharisees which were with them heard
these words, and said unto him, "Are we
blind also?" And Jesus said unto them,
if ye were blind, ye shall have no sin.
But now ye say, we see, so therefore
your sin remainth.
So what he tell you, look, long as
you're blind to something, sure, the
sin's been committed, but it not going
to be held against you. But once you
find out about it, you got to do
something to fix it.
We let them know if you was blind. If if
you was blind, hey, you uh you still
guilty, but it's not held against you.
But he said to these guys, but you said
you see. So if you see, then you are
guilty. So if you didn't know that you
were supposed to get baptized at 20 and
you got baptized at whatever age you got
baptized, once you find out, what you
got to do is get baptized again
when you're 20 and above. That's all I
have to say.
All right, I hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
>> Next one. Skyrider says, "When it talks
about confessing sins, do you have to
list every single act you did? And if
yes, what about those that you forgot?
Cuz this was a long time ago."
>> All right, brother Dre. Most of us too
many sins to count.
>> Yeah.
The book say confess our sins. You know,
confession is to acknowledge and to
admit guilt, to repent. But let's go to
uh Proverbs 28. And we going to read
verse 13. Proverbs 28 and 13. When you
get there, read that, brother.
>> Proverb. Proverbs 28 and 13. Mhm.
>> He that coverth his sin shall not
prosper,
>> but who so confessth and forsaketh them
shall have mercy.
>> So this is what we talking about here is
not covering your sins, you go to the
Lord and repent,
confess them, and not only confess them,
but forsake them,
>> and the Lord will show you mercy. Let's
go to one other place. Let's go to
Ezekiel 18 and we going to read verse 22
there. Ezekiel 18 and 22. When you get
it, go ahead, brother.
>> All his transgression that he have
committed.
>> I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Tanzel. Read 21
and 22.
But if the wicked will turn from all his
sins that he have committed, and keep
all my statutes, and do that which is
lawful and right, he shall surely live.
He shall not die.
>> All his transgression that he have
committed, they shall not be mentioned
unto him. In his righteousness that he
have done, he shall live.
>> That's right. So the Lord wants us to
not only confess our sins, but he want
us to repent and forsake them, turn away
from them, and he will have mercy on us,
and they won't be mentioned. And many of
us have sinned so much, we don't we
can't talk about every sin. So, like you
said, we may have forgotten,
>> but you confess your sins and you ask
the Lord for forgiveness and mean it
>> and forsake them. That's all I got.
>> So, Dre though, he says, "Do you have or
she says, "Do you have to list every
single act you did or sin?" So, if you
have forgotten them, you just lump them
all together or how do you go about
that?
You confess your sins,
>> acknowledge you sinned against God, and
forsake them, and the Lord will forgive
you. That's what we read.
>> That's all right.
>> And and who and who can remember all
their sins? So, what you do is you ask
the Lord to forgive you for all of your
sins.
>> Yes, sir. Absolutely.
>> Yes, sir.
>> That's how you do it.
>> That's it.
>> Yep.
Yep. All right. Hope that answered your
question. Next one.
>> Next one. Be alert as in Revelations
4:E4.
Why Why is the 24 elders associated with
1 Chronicles
24 Aaron's sons?
>> All right. So, they want to know about
that Revelation 4 and 4 and that 1
Chronicles 24 about Aaron's sons. Now
let's go to Revelation 4 and 4 and the
guest caller will take it from there.
>> And round about the throne were four and
20 seats. And upon the seats I saw four
and 20 elders sitting clothed in white
raignment and they had on their heads
crowns of gold.
>> But the whole thing is these 24
[clears throat] elders are not in
heaven.
Right.
>> So they cannot be around the throne. But
who are they? Let's go to 1 Chronicles
the 24th chapter and read verse
5.
>> Read it when you get there.
Thus were they divided by lot one sort
with another. For the governors of the
sanctuary and governors of the house of
God were of the sons of Eleazar and the
sons of Iththear.
>> Now these are the governors of the house
of God. That's that's the temple that's
going to be built by Zerubbabel that
Jesus is going to uh uh uh uh dwell in.
And they are sitting on th and they
going they sitting on throne because
they are going to help Jesus run this
earth. They just have a particular uh uh
uh uh uh uh job to do like David is
going to be king over Israel. But let's
go into Revelation the 5th chapter and
we're going to read from 8 to 10.
Revelation 5 from 8 to 10 and see and
see what these uh uh look at this song
that these guys are singing.
Revelation 5 8-10.
>> And when he had taken the book, the four
beasts and four and 20 elders fell down
before the lamb, having every one of
them harps in golden vows full of odors,
which are the prayers of saints.
And they sung a new song, saying, Thou
are worthy to take the book, and to open
the seals thereof. For thou was slain,
and has redeemed us to God by thy blood
out of every kindric and tongue and
people and nation, and has made us unto
our God, kings and priests, and we shall
reign on the earth.
Now it's mentioned about the four beasts
but the four beast was not redeemed from
among men. It's the 24 elders.
And so when the Lord come and say they
going to make us king and priest and we
going to reign on the earth. Now let's
go and show you. Let's go to 1
Corinthians 6th chapter. We going to
read verse 2 and three.
1 Corinthians 6
and three.
>> And do ye not do ye not know that the
saints shall judge the world? And if the
world shall be judged by you, are ye
unworthy to judge the smallest matters?
But know ye not that we shall judge
angels? How much more things that
pertain to this life?
See, and that's what is coming when
Jesus here for the thousand years that
he going to rule this earth.
Those of us that's going to be in the
first resurrection will have a job to
do. Like I said, David's going to be
king over Israel.
12 apostles are going to be uh uh uh
king over each individual tribe. So, you
going to make you judge over the tribe.
Then you got other people with jobs that
they going to have in this. And so these
24 elders are the sons of Aaron and they
are the governedh.
They are the governors of the sanctuary.
So they come from among men.
They are not in heaven. These people
will going to be in the first
resurrection. So they just set of many
that's going to have job to do during
the thousand years of Jesus reign
but they are the sons of Aaron. That's
all I have to say.
>> All right. I hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next one.
>> Moving on. Ivon Dansancy says, "I'm new
to IOG. What does the Bible say about
smoking?
Uh well first of all welcome to the IOG
and um as far as smoking is concerned
may not be great for your health but
let's go on to first John 3. 1 John 3
and let's pick it up at that verse four.
1 John 3 and 4.
Go ahead. Whosoever committh sins is
transgressive also the law. For sin is
the transgression of the law.
>> So like I say, uh smoking might not be
best for your health, but it's it's not
sin. It's a choice that you make. But
however, if you decide to smoke, no
smoking on the Sabbath day. Let's go to
Exodus 35.
Exodus 35. Because with you being new to
the Israel of God, we want to point this
out to you also in case you are a
smoker. Exodus 35
and let's pick it up at that verse one
and let's see who mentioned about
kindling of fire on the Sabbath day
which is also pertaining to smoking. Go
ahead Tenzel. And Moses gathered all the
congregation of the children of Israel
together, and said unto them, These are
the words which the Lord hath commanded
that ye should do them.
Six days your work be done, but on the
seventh day there shall be to you, and
holy day, a Sabbath of rest to the Lord.
Whosoever doeth work therein shall be
put to death.
You shall kindle no fire throughout your
habitation upon the Sabbath day.
>> All right. So there you go. Kindle no
fire on the Sabbath day. So if you are
smoking for six days, hey, you can
smoke. But on the Lord's Sabbath day, no
smoking. No kindling of fire. And I just
wanted to add in there also that that
pertains to um even the ecigarettes
which are a battery operated device that
heats up the liquid solution inside to
create an aerosol
which produces all that smoke that you
see people when they smoking. So even
your ecigarette should be retired on the
Sabbath day because that's a form of
smoking too. And that's all I got on
that.
All right. We hope that that answered
your question and we go keep moving.
>> Yes. Moving on. Skyrider says, "When the
Messiah comes back to fight wars against
the beast and false prophet and his
armies, are we fighting with him too or
is it just him and his angels or by
himself?"
>> Definitely come back to fight with help.
Brother brother Jerome, what you say?
>> Yeah, those that make that first
resurrection certainly gonna be fighting
alongside the Lord and with the angels.
Okay. Yes. Let's go to um Psalms 149.
>> And we going to read [clears throat]
Yep.
>> 149 and read verse 5-9. And then we
going to go to Daniel's after that.
Tenzel
>> Psalms 1495-9.
>> Yeah.
>> Let the saints be joyful in glory. Let
them sing aloud upon their beds. Let the
high praises of God be in their mouth
and a two-edged sword in their hand.
>> Yep.
>> To execute vengeance upon the evening
and punishment upon the people. To bind
their kings with chains and their nobles
with feathers of iron. to execute upon
them the judgment written. This honor
have all his saints. Praise ye the Lord.
Now, let's tie that with the Daniels
chapter 7 and read verse 17- 18.
These great beasts which are four are
four kings which shall arise out of the
earth. But the saints of the most high
shall take the kingdom and possess the
kingdom forever, even forever and ever.
Then I will know the truth of the fourth
beast which was the verse from all the
other.
>> That's good. That's good. So the saints
going to take the kingdom and we read
that Psalms 1449.
They going to execute that judgment.
They going to take it. That's all I got
on it.
>> Let me read one more. Okay, I want you
to read one. Go to Jude and read verses
14 and 15.
>> All right. The book of Jude. That book
right before Revelations.
>> Jude 14.
>> And Enoch also the seven from Adam
prophesied of these saints. Behold, the
Lord cometh with 10 thousands of his
saints to execute judgment upon all, and
to convince all that are ungodly among
them of all their ungodly deeds which
they have ungodly committed, and of all
their hard speeches, which ungodly
sinners have spoken against him.
So them saints that he going to come
with like uh Jerome said those are going
to be people in the first resurrection
along with the angels that he going to
bring with him.
>> That's all I have to say.
>> Yes sir. They'll be ready. Tanzale.
>> All right.
Move on to our next question.
>> Next question. This person also asks,
"Does a person have to close their eyes
every time they or someone prays or is
that optional?"
>> All right, Dre. Closing your eyes or
leaving them open? Is it optional?
>> Optional. Let's go to uh John 17. We're
going to read verse one. John 17 and
one.
Read that when you get there, brother.
These words spake Jesus and lifted up
his eyes to heaven and said, "Father,
the hour is come. Glorify thy son that
thy son also may glorify thee."
>> So here he lifted up his eyes to heaven.
Now let's go over to uh Matthew 26.
Matthew 26 and look at another instance.
Matthew 26 and read verse 39.
And we gonna skip to I mean 36 and we
gonna skip to 39.
>> Then come up Jesus with him to place
called Gethsemane. Said unto the
disciples, sit ye here while I go and
pray yonder.
>> So Jesus went to pray. Verse 39. Go
ahead. And he went a little further and
fell on his face and prayed,
>> saying, "Oh my father, if it be
possible, let this cup pass from me."
>> So he fell on his face.
>> He fell on his face here. The other one
he lifted up his eyes. Now let's go to
one more place. Let's go to First Kings
8.
First Kings 8. And we going to read
verse 22.
Read it when you get there, brother.
>> First Kings 8.
>> And Solomon stood before the altar of
the Lord in the presence of all the
congregation of Israel and spread forth
his hands towards heaven.
>> So Solomon spread forth his hands. So
it's optional. That's your answer.
That's all I got.
>> All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question,
>> next one. Linda Stringer says, "In Luke
3, in the genealogology of Jesus, it
says Canaan was the son of our fax,
but Canaan is not reflected in the
Chronicles genealogy.
However, it is reflected in some other
translations."
All right, brother Jerome,
share some light.
>> Yeah, we don't we don't read those other
translations. We don't we don't trust in
in the text, okay? We read the King
James Version Bible and that's where we
get our our source of information from,
okay? The word of God. Uh but uh let's
go read that verse that you gave though
in that Luke
Let me see.
>> Luke 3.
It he uh they just Luke, right? It just
says in Luke 3.
>> I think it's um 37.
>> Yeah, 36 too picks up which is the son
of Canaan.
>> Okay. 36 and 37. Thank you.
>> You're welcome, brother.
which was the son of Canaan, which was
the son of Araxad, which was the son of
Sim, which was the son of No, which was
the son of Lame.
>> Yeah, that's good enough. That's good
enough. Yeah. Now, uh, a fact said he
had several sons
and daughters
and all of their names,
they not, you know, they not mentioned
in the Bible. Not all of them. Okay. So,
now let's go to Genesis chapter 11 and
read verse 13.
with Genesis 11.
>> Yeah.
>> And verse 13.
>> And our fact live after he begott 43
years and begott sons and daughters.
>> Okay. So now
we got two names that I mentioned that
we can read. We just read Sah
here in Genesis 11. And then in your
question you gave the Luke chapter 3
which was I think verse 36 right
Cornell.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Where you where you saw the K and
then how or however you pronounce it. At
least those two are mentioned but he had
several other sons and daughters too and
their names are not mentioned. Okay.
>> That that's all I got on there.
>> Yeah. All right. And like you said too,
brother, King James version is all we
need to get salvation.
All right, we're gonna keep it moving to
our next one.
>> Next one. Sky Rider wants you to explain
Isaiah 19 verse 25 where he calls
Egyptians his people. Also, why is
Israel a third party to Egypt and
Assyria in verse 24?
All right. So, looks like that first
question pertains to Isaiah 19 and 25.
Tanzel
where he calls the Egyptians his people.
Let's go there and uh read that in the
guest caller and take it from there.
>> Yeah, we should change.
>> We should change the title of this
program is to skyriter. Don't we have a
policy?
Yeah, we just uh instituted a policy
tonight that no more than two questions
will be taken from any viewer.
>> Not [clears throat] tonight. You've been
saying it all along.
>> Yeah,
>> but I deal with this. Go ahead.
>> Isaiah 19 and 25.
>> Whom the Lord?
>> Go ahead.
whom the Lord of hosts shall bless,
saying, "Blessed be Egypt, my people,
and Assyria, the work of my hands, and
Israel my inheritance."
>> The re the reason, you know, it just he
just didn't name all of it. You
understand? just Egypt and and uh uh uh
Assyria and just nations out of all the
nation that are become are going to uh
uh uh be called by the Lord his people.
Let's go to Isaiah the 56th chapter read
1 2 3
from 1 to 3
and then we're going to skip.
Thus sayeth the Lord, keep the judgment
and do justice, for my salvation is near
to come, and my righteousness to be
revealed. But blessed is the man that
doeth this, and the son of man that lay
up hold on it, that keepeth the Sabbath
from polluting it, and keepeth his hand
from doing any evil. Neither let the son
of the stranger that have joined himself
to the Lord, speak, saying, The Lord
have utterly separated me from his
people. Neither let the unit say,
"Behold, I am a dry tree."
>> Now look, he said, "Neither let the son
of the stranger." That's cover all of
the sons of Adam. That's not talking
about Israel.
>> About Israel
utterly separated me from his people.
Skip down to verse six. Let's see what
he going to say to the son of the
stranger. 6 through8.
also the sons of the stranger that join
themselves to the Lord to serve him and
to love the name of the Lord to be his
servants. Everyone that keepeth the
Sabbath from polluting it and take up
hold of my covenant. Even then when I
bring to my holy mountain and make them
joyful in my house of prayer, their
burnt offerings and their sacrifices
shall be accepted upon my altar. For my
house shall be called an house of prayer
for all people. The Lord God which
gathered the Alis of Israel said yet I
gather others to him besides those that
are gathered unto him.
>> So that included all nations. Go to
Zechariah the second chapter and read 8
through 11.
Zechariah 28-11.
For thus sayith the Lord of hosts, after
the glory hath he sent me unto the
nations which spoiled you. For he that
toucheth you touches the apple of his
eye. For behold, I will shake my hand
upon them, and they and they shall be a
spoil to their servants, and ye shall
know that the Lord of hosts have hath
sent me. Sing and rejoice, oh daughter
of Zion, for lo, I come, and I will
dwell in the midst of thee, sayeth the
Lord. And many nations shall be joined
to the Lord in that day, and shall be my
people, and I will dwell in the midst of
thee, and thou shalt know
>> that the Lord of hosts have sent me unto
thee.
>> Well, that's why he said many nations,
that's all nations,
>> going to be joined.
>> So, let's go into St. John the 10th
chapter.
We're going to read verse 1.
Then we're going to skip down and read
9- 11 and verse 16.
Verily, verily, I say unto you, he
either enterth not by the door into the
sheepfold, but climbth up some other
way, the same is a thief and a robber.
>> Skip down to nine.
I am the door. By me. If any man enter
in, he shall be saved and shall go in
and out and find pasture.
>> Read to 11.
>> The thief cometh not for to steal and to
kill and to destroy. I am come that they
might have life and that they might ha
might have it more abundantly. I am the
good shepherd. The good shepherd giveth
his life for the sheep.
>> Down to 16.
>> And other sheep I have which are not of
this fold. Them also I must bring and
they shall hear my voice. And there
shall be one fold and one shepherd.
>> That mean that that mean they all are
going to be the children of God just
like Israel is.
>> Right. But then the Lord let us know
that when he sent Moses down into Egypt
to go to one last place,
Exodus the 4th chapter, read 21 and 22.
And the Lord said unto Moses, "When thou
goest to return unto Egypt, see that
thou do all those wonders before
Pharaoh, which I have put in thy hand,
but I will harden his heart, that he
shall not let the people go." And thou
shalt say unto Pharaoh, Thus sayeth the
Lord, Israel is my son, even my
firstborn.
>> Go ahead.
>> And I say unto thee, let my son go that
he may serve me. If thou refuse to let
him go, behold, I will slay thy son,
even thy firstborn.
>> Okay, so he let him know Israel is a
son, even his firstborn, the whole
nation. Firstborn mean he going to adopt
to adopt the rest of the nations. So now
he just named Egypt and Assyria, but all
of the nations are going to be the
nations and the people of God and the
children of God. everyone of the son
out of every one of the sons of Noah.
The Lord going to adopt all of these
nations. We just named the three. That's
all I have to say.
>> Yep. All right. We hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one with a time check.
>> Yes, the time is 8:13.
Adam says, "I've heard brother Buoie
mention that we know
>> uh the Lord will come back on the day of
atonement. Can you please explain so
that I may gain understanding?"
>> All right, we're going to ask the guest
caller, can you represent Brother Bully
on this question?
>> Let's go to Leviticus the 25th chapter.
We're going to read 8 9 and skip down to
13.
Leviticus 25, pick up at verse 8.
>> Yep.
>> And thou shalt number seven Sabbaths of
years unto thee. Seven times seven
years, and the space of the seven
Sabbaths of years shall be unto thee 40
and 9 years. Then shalt thou cause the
trumpet of the jubilee to sound on the
10th day of the seventh month. And the
day of atonement shall ye make the
trumpet sound throughout all your gen
all your land.
And you shall hollow the
>> go.
>> And you shall hollow the 50th year and
proclaim liberty throughout all the land
unto all the inhabitants thereof. It
shall be a jubilee unto you, and you
shall return every man unto his
possession, and ye shall return every
man unto his family.
So now that is when the Lord come.
That's why he said everybody going to
turn to their own people and free to
their own land. And the Lord going to
recover Israel. But when is this going
to start?
On the day of atonement. That's when you
have the trumpet of Jubilee to sound.
What trumpet is that? That is the
seventh trumpet. Let's go into Isaiah
the 27th chapter and read verse 13.
Isaiah 27
and verse 13.
Mhm.
>> And it shall come to pass on that day
that the great trumpet shall be blown,
and they shall come which were ready to
perish in the land of Assyria, and the
outcasts in the land of Egypt, and shall
worship the Lord in the holy mount at
Jerusalem.
>> Now, that's that's the seventh trumpet
that's going to be blown on Jubilee on
the uh uh day of atonement. Now, let's
go into Matthew the 24th chapter.
We're going to read 27. Then we going to
jump down to 29-31.
>> Matthew 24.
>> For as a lightning cometh,
>> verse 27 first. Mhm.
For as the lightning cometh out of the
east and shineth even unto the west, so
shall also the coming of the son of man
be.
>> Skip down to verse 39 and read to uh 29
rather and read to verse 31.
Immediately after the tribulation of
those days shall the sun be darkened,
and the moon shall not give her light,
and the stars shall fall from heaven,
and the powers of heaven shall be
shaken. And then shall appear the sign
of the son of man in heaven. And then
shall all the tribes of the earth mourn,
and they shall see the son of man coming
[clears throat] in the clouds of heaven
with power and great glory. And he shall
send his angels with a great sound of a
trumpet. And they shall gather together
his elect from the four winds from one
end of the heaven to the other.
>> That's going to be on the on on the on
the day of atonement. That's the seventh
trump. Got two more places. 1
Thessalonians 4 and read verse 16.
For the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with a shout, with the voice of
the archangel, and with the trump of
God. And the dead in Christ shall rise
first.
Then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air.
>> So we going to descend from heaven on
what day? the day of atonement and then
the trumpet going to be blown,
>> right?
>> And the dead in Christ going to be
raised
and the living and the uh uh uh uh
living change. One other place 1
Corinthians the 15th chapter, we're
going to read verse 50
to 52.
Now this I say, brethren, that flesh and
blood cannot inherit the kingdom of God,
neither do corruption inherit
incorruption.
Behold, I show you a mystery. We shall
not all sleep, but we shall all be
changed
in a moment, in a twinkling of an eye,
at the last trump. For the trump shall
sound, and the dead shall be raised
incorruptible, and we shall be changed.
>> Soon now when the Lord comes on the day
of atonement, the trumpet is going to be
s going to be blown, then the dead going
to be raised, people going to be
gathered,
and the Lord is going to take over this
earth. when at the seventh trumpet which
is the last trumpet which is
going to be blown
on the day of atonement. Like I said in
Leviticus the 25th chapter. That's all I
have to say.
>> All right.
>> Much more much more I could read but we
ain't going to read all night. Okay.
That's it.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question. Next one.
>> Uh next one. And again, this uh uh these
are held over questions. And so we do
have uh a couple of more from Sky Rider
uh for this uh night. Uh he says, "Is it
true that early humans were taller like
giants because of sin? We got shorter
now." Some churches teach that Adam and
Eve were like 20 feet and 18 feet tall,
respectively.
All right. Be careful. Some of them
churches. Go ahead, brother. Uh Julius,
you on mute.
First of all, um, next time somebody
tell you, uh, these churches tell you
Adam and Eve was 20 and 18 feet tall,
tell them to give you book, chapter, and
verse. That's number one. Number two,
let's go to Genesis the 6th chapter.
Genesis the 6th chapter.
Let's look Well, let's look at why God
uh cut man's time down.
Verse one, 10, we going to read one to
three.
Well, we going to just keep reading to
four. Go ahead.
>> And it came to pass when men began to
multiply on the face of the earth, and
daughters were born unto them, that the
sons of God saw the daughters of men
that they were fair. And they took them
wise of all which they choose.
>> So now we got man, we got woman, and we
got marriage. For what? For producing
children.
Okay, go ahead and read. And the Lord
said, "My spirit shall not always strive
with man, for that he also is flesh,
that his days shall be 120 years." My
spirit shall not always strive with man
because this man is going to eventually
sin. And the wages of sin is death, not
shortness.
The wages of sin is death, not
shortness. Now, let's look at these
giants that was also there in those in
the in the same days. Go ahead.
There were giants in the earth in those
days. And also after that, when the sons
of God came in unto the daughters of
men, and they bear children to them, the
same became mighty men which were of old
men.
>> So now this is not angels because angels
are are do not reproduce. These sons of
God are the sons of Adam and Seth that
lay with the daughters of Cain, which
were women. So angels do not reproduce.
flesh and blood reproduces. Now, how
tall was these giants? Let's go to
numbers to show you that there was not
everybody was tall in them days. Go
ahead. Numbers the 13th chapter. Tanzel.
Let's look what Moses did.
We got giants in these days. We call
them big tall people.
Numbers 13
and read verse 16 to 18. When you get
it, go ahead, brother.
These are the names of the men which
Moses sent to spy out the land. And
Moses called Osha, the son of N uh
Jehoshap.
>> In other words, this is Joshua.
Continue.
>> And Moses sent them to spy out the land
of Canaan and said unto them, get you up
this way southward and go up into the
mountain and see the land. What is it?
And the people that dwell there and
>> and the people
and the people. Go ahead. whether they
be strong or weak, few or many.
>> Now, skip down, my brother. When Moses
sent Joshua and Caleb, because that's
who he sent, Joshua and Caleb to the
land of Canaan to spy the land. Show you
everybody wasn't the same size compared
to Joshua and Caleb. Look what they said
in verse 33 about these giants. Go
ahead.
And there we saw the giants of the sons
of Anch.
>> The sons of Anch that they were Anakims,
big tall people that had mamas and
daddies and brothers and sisters. Go
ahead and read.
>> Which come of the giants and we were in
our own sight as grasshoppers
and so we were in their sight.
>> So everybody know the basketball player
Shaquille O'Neal. Now, if you put a
next to Shaquille O'Neal, in the
eyes of the he he's going to
look like a giant. And the is
going to look at himself as a
grasshopper in time in in terms of uh
height.
Let's go to one last place. 1st Samuel
17. 1st Samuel 17. You see, it's too
many myths and fables when you all we
got to do is read the book.
1st Samuel 17 and I got one verse. This
is uh Goliath, the one that David
killed, a giant that can die. Can't kill
an angel. Read verse four, brother.
>> 1 Samuel uh 17.
>> 17-4.
>> And there went out a champion out of the
camp of the Philistines named Goliath of
G whose height was 6 cubit and a span.
today that equals 9'9 in but still a
fleshy man that David end up killing. So
it is not true that early humans would
uh or taller like giants except the ones
that are counted giants like the Anakims
like the Zumaims
the sons of Anoch and David killed
Goliath and David's men killed four
other giants because these are flesh and
blood men with
uh mothers and fathers. So that's the
answer to that question. So I I want I
want to correct that. Somebody said
respectively, "No, these churches is
teaching falsehood. Read the book."
That's all I got. Cornell.
>> All right, we'll leave it right there
and keep moving.
>> Moving on.
>> Hold on, Deborah. One second. Guest
caller.
>> Look, the scripture say the Lord cut
their years down, not this statue.
>> Thank you.
You still got people 9 ft on this earth.
>> Check up with Man B.
>> Go look at some of the African tribes.
Look at some of the African tribes. They
got people that average 9 ft.
>> Yep. All right. So, we know we shed some
light on that question. Next question.
>> Next one. Brick Bratz says, "Can you
help me explain to my friends why they
need to use the KJV Bible over the New
Translation ones?" I told them about
scriptures being removed from those
Bibles plus gave them Revelation 22
18 and 19.
>> All right. They want to know about why
should they use a KJV known as a King
James version. Brother Julius,
let's go to Revelation
the 22nd chapter and show you why you
should not read these new translations.
We read the KJV because it is
commissioned by God and it is proven by
prophecy.
Now, let's look at the new translations,
what they done to it. Read verse
Revelation 22 and instead of uh going to
um 18, let's read start at verse 16.
>> Jesus here. Go ahead.
>> I Jesus have sent my angels to testify
unto you these things of the churches.
>> Uhhuh.
>> I am the root and the offspring of David
and the bright and morning star. Skip
down to verse 18. Now,
>> for I testify unto every man that he
hearth the words of the prophecy of this
book,
>> of this book, KJV,
KJV, of this book, which is the book of
the Lord according to Isaiah 34:16.
Read.
>> If any man shall add unto these things,
God shall add unto him the plagues that
are written in this book. Mhm.
>> Any man shall take away from the words
of the book of this prophecy, God shall
take away his part out of the book of
life and out of the holy city and from
the things which are written in this
book.
>> So now this is why we read the KJV. It
go from Genesis to Revelation.
Everything that you need for salvation
and how to avoid being in the lake of
fire. shows you the coming of the Lord,
shows you how to live and conduct
yourself, shows you where you come from
and what God intends you to be. All
these other translations got hundreds
and or either thousands of changes in uh
in words and in scriptures and even some
that add scriptures such as the lost
book, such as the apocrypha and so on
and so forth. So stick with the KJV. It
is enough in it. It is it is
commissioned by God and it is proven by
prophecy. That's all I got. Cornell.
>> That's right, brother Joseph. And King
James version matches up with world
history
>> and it and it's proven by history. So
therefore, it is only called the King
James version because it's written in
the King's language, which is English.
>> Yep. All right. Thank you for that,
brother. Hope that answered their
question. Next one.
>> Next one. Linda Stringer says in
Revelation 5:es 1-5,
it describes men in heaven around the
throne of God and no man could open the
book. You have taught that men do not go
to heaven. It says men are at the throne
of God in heaven.
>> All right. Well, first of all, you got
to know that angels are also called men
and that we the book has taught us that
men do not go to heaven. But let's go
into that revelation that they talking
about at Revelation 5 1-5
and go right ahead and let's see in that
verse two who we talking about here. Go
ahead, brother.
>> Verse two.
>> Uh verse one.
And I saw in the right hand of him that
sat on the throne, a book written within
and on the backside sealed with seven
seals.
>> Uhhuh.
>> I saw a strong angel proclaiming with a
loud voice, who is worthy to open the
book and to loose the seals thereof.
>> So we talking about an angel here in
heaven. Go ahead.
>> No man in heaven nor in earth, neither
under the earth was able to open the
book, neither to look there.
And I wept much because no man was found
worthy to open and to read the book,
neither to look thereon.
>> Mhm.
>> One of the elders said unto me, "Weep
not. Behold, the lion of the tribe of
Judah, the root of David have prevailed
to open the book, and to loose the seven
seals thereof."
>> And because we know no man has ever
ascended to heaven, but he that came
down from heaven, we know that this is
not men in heaven. This is angels being
called men. Let's go quickly to Genesis
19. Genesis 19.
And then we gonna go to Daniel 9. And
that'll be it. Genesis 19, brother.
Let's go there quickly. Dealing. This is
dealing with Lot here. And when he saw
the angels coming and let's see what the
people called those angels. But Genesis
19, pick it up at that verse one. Go
ahead, brother. And there came two
angels to Sodom at evening. And Lot sat
at the gate of Sodom. And Lot seeing
them rose up to meet them. And he bowed
himself with his face towards the
ground.
>> So here come two angels. And when Lot
saw him, he bowed himself down to meet
them. Let's go to verse four and five.
And let's see what the angels were
called by the men. Go ahead. But before
they laid down the men of the city, even
the men of Sodom, compass the house
round, both old and young, all the
people from every quarter.
And they called on Lot, and said unto
him, Where are the men which came in to
thee this night? Bring them out unto us
that we may know them. All right, we not
going to get in the whole story of that,
but we see that the men of the city,
both young and old, called the angels
here men. Now, let's go into Daniel 9,
Daniel the 9th chapter,
and we're going to pick it up at that
verse three. When you get there, Daniel
9 and verse three, and then we're going
to skip down, brother, to 20 and 21. Go
right ahead.
And I set my face unto the Lord God to
seek by prayer and supplication with
fasting and sackloths and ashes.
>> And so this is Daniel here. And he was
fasting with sackcloth and ashes because
he was looking for an answer. Skip down
to verse 20 and 21. Let's see who came
and brought him an answer. Go ahead.
While I was speaking and praying and
confessing my sin and the sins of my
people Israel, presenting my
supplications before the Lord my God,
for the holy mountain of my God. Yeah.
While I was speaking in prayer, even the
man Gabriel, whom I seen in the vision
at the beginning, being caused to fly
swiftly, touched me about the time of
the evening oblation. So even the man
Gabriel which was also an angel was
called a man here. And there's so many
other places that we can go and show
that angels are also called men in some
scriptures. And that's all I got on
that. This was angels being called men.
>> Plus I want you to go read something
that Jesus said.
>> All right. Concern St. John the 3
chapter.
Read verse 13.
St. John 3 and 13.
And no man have ascended up to heaven,
but he that came down from heaven, even
the son of man which is in heaven.
>> And that is it.
>> Yep. That is it. And thus says the book.
As we continue to move on to our next
question,
>> moving on. Skyrider asks, "What does it
mean wine is a marker in Proverbs 20?"
>> Wine is a marker, Brother Dre.
>> Let's go to that Proverbs 20 and read
verse one.
Read it when you get there. Tanzel,
>> wine is a mocker, strong drink is
raging, and whosoever is deceived
thereby is not wise. Yeah. Mocka meaning
you gonna make mockery or be made
mockery of
>> and strong drink is raging. It can be
raging if if you are deceived by it. So
we going to look at that and see how
that happens. Let's go to Proverbs 23
>> and uh look at something right there.
Proverbs 23:29
to35. Go ahead when you get it, brother.
>> Who have woke, who have sorrow, who have
contentions, who have babbling, who have
wounds without cause, who have redness
of eyes.
>> Mhm.
>> And then that terry long at the wine,
that they go to seek mix wine.
>> Wait a minute. It says, "They that tar
long at the wine, and they that go to
seek mixed wine, they got woe, sorrow,
contentions, babbling." Because that's
what it says in Proverbs.
It's strong drink is raging, and wine is
a mocker, you know, and whosoever is
deceived thereby is not wise. Skip down
and read verse 33. Go ahead. Thine eye
shall behold strange women, and thy
heart shall utter perverse things.
>> That's what happens sometimes when
people are oified off of alcohol. They
they behold strange women and they utter
perverse things. Skip down and read
verse 35. Go ahead.
>> They have stricken me. Shall thou say,
and I was not sick? They have beaten me
and I felt it not. When shall I await? I
will seek it yet again.
>> Now listen, for some people, one drink
is too many and a thousand ain't enough.
>> So if that's the problem, that's the
thing. It's excess. But let's look at
one more thing. Let's go to Proverbs 31
and read verse 6. Proverbs 31 and 6.
Read that when you get it.
>> Give strong drink unto him that is ready
to perish.
>> Mhm.
>> And wine unto those that be of heavy
hearts.
>> Yes, sir. Go ahead.
>> Let him drink and forget his poverty.
And remember his misery no more.
>> Hey, the book talks about wine makes the
heart joyous too. It's just excessive,
>> right?
>> Can cause those problems. And if we are
deceived thereby. So that's what it's
talking about. The mockery is
>> you going to be made a mockery of
>> or are you going to mock one or the
other and rage comes with it. A lot of
people drink and want to fight.
>> Some people drink and want to make love.
You know, it's a lot of things happen
>> with that. But that's all I got on that.
>> Yep. All right. Know your limits, right,
Dre? Yes, sir.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
>> Go right ahead. Guest call.
>> Again, too, the first miracle that Jesus
made was wine.
>> And then again, too, he drank so much
wine that they call him a wine bill.
>> They sure did.
>> That's right. And a drunkard.
>> Yes, sir.
>> So, what what what's mockery about
Jesus?
>> Exactly.
Yep.
>> Exactly. Don't be deceived by it. That's
all.
>> Yep. That's it. All right. Hope that
answered your question. Next question.
Time check.
>> Yes. Time is 8:38. Rosyn Hayes asks, "Is
it a sin to watch a Christmas movie?" Uh
>> oh. No, it ain't sin to watch a
Christmas movie. But let's go to that.
First John 3.
First John 3 and verse 4.
Whosoever committh sin transgresseth
also the law. For sin is the
transgression of the law.
>> Yep. So, no, it's not a sin to watch a
Christmas movie, but um make sure you
teach your children and your children's
children all about Christmas and arm
them also. That's all I got
as we continue to move on to our next
question.
>> Next one. Skyw writer says, "If a person
was baptized under 20 years old and
found out the truth after 20 years old,
then should that
then should they then get rebaptized?"
>> All right. G caller baptized under 20,
found out the truth. Should you be
rebaptized when you are 20?
>> Question is yes.
Go to Leviticus the 5th chapter, read
verses four and skip down and read
verses six.
Or if a soul swear, pronouncing with his
lips to do evil or to do good,
whatsoever it be that a man shall
pronounce with an oath, and it be hid
from him, when he knoweth of it, then he
shall be guilty in one of these.
>> Now it say you do something and it's hid
from you. In other words, you do
whatever it is, even baptizing, you
don't know better. You know, you are
still uh uh guilty. But what happened?
Skip down and read verse six.
>> And he shall bring his trespass offering
unto the Lord for his sin which he hath
sinned. A female from the flock of a
lamb or a kid of the goat for a sin
offering. And the priest shall make an
atonement for him concerning his sin.
>> So now so once you find out that you
have done you have done wrong or you
have not done the right thing, then you
go and you do it. Now animals uh uh
blood was offered for you. But what you
do is when you go go get bapti when you
go get baptized that's your sacrifice
because you're under the blood of Jesus
now. So since you find out
that you should be 20 or older to get
baptized
do it
>> right
>> that's the end of it.
>> Yeah.
>> And if you're a male you must be
circumcised.
Mhm.
>> Of course.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question. Next one.
>> Yes. Here another Bible question. Uh
Linda Stringer asks, "Why don't
believers
use the Septuagent
Bible as it was supposed to be
translated first by Egyptian Jews before
AD?"
>> All right, here we go with another
Bible. Brother Julius, go right ahead.
>> Why don't believers believe in the
Septuagent Bible? Because that is a
Greek translation.
That is a Greek translation of the uh
supposed to be the Hebrew Bible. Notice
always the another name for the the
actually the word Septuagent is Latin
for 70. That's why you see LXX next to
it. So the question is
uh why don't believers use the
Septuagent Bible? Because believers use
the KJV. And let me show you what
believers believe when the two church
started. Let's go to Acts the 7th
chapter.
Acts chapter 7. And we're going to read
one verse. Acts 7 uh Tenzel. And when
you get it, read verse 38. Well, this is
this is Stefan,
the Israelite Stefan who ran down
Israel's whole history. Surely he should
have mentioned Septu, but he didn't.
This is talking about and he went to
talk about Moses. Let's look at where
the two started at. Not in Greece, not
in Rome.
Let's look over where the church started
at. Go ahead. Act pick it up at verse
37. Go ahead. This is that Moses, which
said unto the children of Israel, a
prophet shall the Lord your God raise up
unto you of your brethren, like unto me.
Him shall ye hear.
>> Uh-huh.
>> This is he that was in the church in the
wilderness.
>> The church in Rome
>> in the wilderness.
>> Go ahead. with an angel which spake to
him in the mount si and with our fathers
who received the lively oracles to give
unto us.
>> So the oracles are answers. The answers
was given to Israel. The covenants were
made with Israel. Read Romans the ninth
chapter. Paul will tell you that the
ministry given to Israel, not to the
Egyptian Jews in Alexandria.
uh what you uh theh at the end of your
question AD AD what AD3 the third in the
3rd century
that's the 300s so therefore uh this is
why true believers don't use the
Septuagent it's got all them extra books
in there and is never it is not ordained
by God and the uh the prophets never
mention it the disciples never mention
it Jesus never mention
And the the last scripture uh is uh uh
uh uh uh given to as we stated in the
previous questions
revelation 22 he said if they speak not
according to the things that are written
in this book not the septuagent it's
myths fables and lies in those books
compared to the KJV
so that's all I got on that Egyptian
Jews you mean and Alexandria and the
book was already written
First five books were written by Moses.
Has nothing to do with no Egyptian Jews.
That's all I got.
>> All right. Hope that answered that
question. Next question as time is
ticking.
>> Yes. Valencia asked for you to explain
Isaiah 3 verse 1. What do the word stay
uh speak of here?
>> Isaiah 3 and1. Brother Dre.
Isaiah 3 and1. Let's read that, brother
Tanzel. Read it when you get it.
>> For behold, the Lord, the Lord of hosts
do take away from Jerusalem and from
Judea, the stay and the staff, the whole
stay of bread and the whole stay of
water.
>> So that that is talking about his his
support, him being your supplier and
your supporter. But let's go over to
Psalms 18 and read verse 18.
Psalms 18. We going to read verses
17 and 18.
>> Say when you get it. Yep. Psalms 18:17
and 18.
>> He delivered me from my strong enemy and
from them which hate me. For they were
too strong for me.
>> They prevented me in the day of thy
calamity. But the Lord was my state.
>> He said, "They prevented me in the day
of my calamity, but the Lord was my
state. The Lord was my supplier,
comforter, and deliverer,
and support in that that way." Let's go
over to Psalms 105 right quick. Psalm
and read verse 16. Go ahead when you get
it, brother.
Moreover, he called for a famine upon
the land, and he break the whole staff
of bread.
>> Uhhuh. So bread is what we need, and
water is what we need for our
nourishment. But the Lord is our
supplier of both of all things, whether
it be bread and water, spiritual word,
all of that. So that stay is him being
our supplier. That's all I got. Yes sir.
Even to this day.
>> Yes sir.
>> All right. Thank you for that brother.
Our next question sis.
>> Next question. Skyrider says if Baroo
wrote from the mouth of Jeremiah all the
words of the Lord. Jeremiah 36 verse4 is
given. Then would that make the book of
Baroo liable? I mean reliable.
>> All right, let's go to that uh Jeremiah
and they got in question about the verse
four and the guest caller take it from
there. Tanzania
Jeremiah uh 36 and verse4
>> correct.
>> Then Jeremiah called Baroo the son of
Niah. And Baroo wrote from the mouth of
Jeremiah all the words of the Lord which
he has spoken unto him upon the role of
a book.
>> Okay. How many times we going to have we
going to answer this same question.
>> Yeah. That uh
>> yeah that's the final one for our
session this evening from him.
>> I'm going deal with it. But the whole
thing is look
he but Baroo wrote it because Baroo was
a scribe.
>> Yep.
>> And the scribes write what the prophets
and the and and and and what Israel did
over all.
Moses didn't write all the five books
with his hand. He had scribes.
And the scribes had knowledge
of what the prophet spoke.
So the scribe didn't didn't deal with
God. God didn't deal with the scribe. He
dealt with the prophet. I give you a
good example. Let's go into Matthew.
Show you who do the right. Matthew the 2
chapter read 1-5.
>> Matthew 2.
>> Yeah.
>> 1-5.
Now when Jesus was born in Bethlehem of
Judea in the days of Herod the king,
behold there came wise men from the east
of Jerusalem, saying, Where is he that
is born king of the Jews? For we have
seen his star in the east, and I come to
worship him. When Herod the king had
heard these things, he was troubled in
all Jerusalem with him. And when he had
gathered all the chief priests and
scribes of the people together, he
demanded of them where Christ should be
born. And they said unto him, "In
Bethlehem of Judea, for thus it is
written by the prophet."
>> Now when Herod come and demand it, who
did he come to? The scribes and the
Pharisees.
>> Why the scribe? Because these scribes
are the one that writes all of the words
that comes out of the prophet. So what
did they did? Bethlehem, Judea. Why?
because it is written by the prophet.
>> Scribe is another writer. That was their
job.
It's all that simple. It's just like
somebody giving instruction or putting
down laws,
setting laws for a particular uh uh
company. What do they do? They go to
somebody with a typewriter. They are
typers. They type down the message.
>> What message? The message that they
given by somebody else. who it is by the
scribe. He is a writer and the writer
writes what the prophets say because the
prophet because God deals with the
prophet. So that's why it's not the book
of Baroo. A lot of times he wrote stuff
that the scribe wrote stuff that they
didn't understand. They just wrote what
they was told to write.
And that's all I have to say about that.
>> All right. I hope that answered your
question. Next question.
Next one. Mark Ash says, "I watched IOG
Phoenix and a woman was the reader. Is
this in order?"
>> All right. A sister read the word,
Brother Julius.
Yes, it's Yes, it's very much in order.
And I'm going show you why it's in
order. Let's go to Let's go to Joel, the
second chapter. Let's do this quick.
Tenzel Joel 2,
the book of Joel 2. And we're going to
read verse 28 and 29.
A woman
cannot usurp the authorities. She cannot
be behind the pull pit pull pit. But we
going to read that to you. Joel 2, read
28 and 29, brother. When you get it, go
ahead.
>> And it shall come to pass afterward that
I will pour out my spirit upon all
flesh.
>> Uhhuh.
Your sons and your daughters shall
prophesize.
>> No, only your son, only your sons.
>> Your sons and your daughters.
>> Go ahead, brother.
>> Your old men shall dream dreams. Your
young men shall see visions and also
upon the servants and upon the
handmmaids and those
>> upon the upon only the male servants
>> and the handmaids.
>> Handmaids. Go ahead.
>> And in those days will I pour out my
spirit. Now, let's go to Acts the 2
chapter. Let's look at the prophecy that
was fulfilled on the day of Pentecost.
Acts 2 and pick it up at verse 16.
The Bible, this is why we read the KJV
because the book said the prophets are
subject unto the prophets. Now, let's
look at what Joel prophesied and let's
look at what Peter is testifying. Go
ahead. Verse 16.
But this is that which was spoken by the
prophet Joel.
>> We just read that. Go ahead. What
happened?
>> It shall come to pass in the last days,
said God, I will pour out my spirit upon
all flesh, and your sons and your
daughters shall prophesy.
>> Yes.
>> Your young men shall see visions, and
your old men shall dream dreams.
>> So that's why you have prophetesses,
Miriam, Holder. You have prophetesses in
the Bible that can speak the word of
God. In order to do that, they have to
read the book.
They can read the book. Continue at
verse 18.
>> And on my servants and on my
handmaidaidens,
I will pour out in those days of my
spirit. They prophesy.
>> So now, let's go to First Timothy
chapter 2. 1 Timothy chapter 2. We're
gonna read verse 11 and 12. Because
there the Lord said, do all things
decent and in order.
>> Let the woman learn in silence with all
subjection.
>> Uh-huh.
>> But I suffer not a woman to teach.
>> I suffer not a woman to read,
>> to teach.
>> There you go.
>> Nor to usurp authority over the man.
>> Uhhuh.
>> But to be in silence.
>> So she can learn in silence. But when
she get that book and that spirit of the
Lord come over her, she can prophesy.
That means speak that which is already
written. Her job is not to be behind the
pull pit. She cannot be the head of a
church. There are no female deaconists
in the Bible. So therefore,
that's the only thing she's restricted.
She cannot be behind. She could be she
can serve in the church. She could she
could be a female usher in the church,
but she cannot be behind the pull pit.
So yes, what you saw in Phoenix and
anywhere else in Isl.
It's allowed. She just can't be behind
the pull pit. That's all I got.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question as time is a ticking. Let's
move on to the next one.
>> Yes. King Iikable says, "Being in the
truth and planning on owning a group
home, how do I enforce the dietary law
being that my clients will be provided
by the state and other government
agencies?
Is it right to tell them not to put up a
Christmas tree and celebrate Christmas,
Easter, and put up Halloween decorations
in my group home?"
Right. Owning a group home. What do you
do? Guest caller.
Well, you do what the people that's
paying you the money to do.
Now, if you don't want to do that, then
maybe you should seek another form,
another career.
Because if the government's going to pay
for them, then the government is the one
that's going to dictate what they can or
cannot have.
Now, if you want to open up a group home
and don't accept no money from nobody
and pay it out of your own pocket, then
you can dictate what they can or cannot
have. That's all I have to say.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
>> Next one. Sai Amu uh Sai Amaru Israel
asks, "Is it okay to take advantage of
sales during the holidays? I know we
don't celebrate them, but is it okay to
purchase the do uh the discount prices
or should we not shop during this time
like groceries and clothing, etc.?"
>> Oh, you can you can feel free to shop
during that time.
as they say sometimes, shop till you
drop.
And that's that's all I got on that.
>> Who won't take advantage of a discount?
>> Yeah, they have good discounts during
this time. So, hey, feel free to go out
there and take advantage of it. All
right, Sister Deborah, our next
question. Yes, the same person asked,
"Is Jesus going to reign on David's
throne or is David going to reign?"
Please explain Luke 1 verse 32 and
Ezekiel 37
24 and 25.
>> All right, Brother Jerome, who's gonna
be on David's throne?
I think you kind of misunderstanding how
that David's throne work. It's not a
it's not just a singular throne. Okay.
Uh it's many thrones that represent the
throne of David. Uh that Jesus going to
be sitting on and everybody in the first
resurrection going to be sitting on.
They actually going to be sitting on
what's called the throne of David. Jesus
and everybody in the first resurrection.
Okay? So, it's not one throne that
everybody trying to pile up on. Okay.
So, let's go. Um,
look at Psalms 122 verse 5.
Psalms 122:5.
When you get it, go ahead and read.
>> Well, there I set thrones of judgment.
>> See, that's plural. Set thrones of
judgment. Go ahead.
>> The thrones of the house of David.
>> Yeah.
>> And so that's a throne that not only
Jesus going to sit on, David going to
sit on that throne, too. And everybody
in the first resurrection going to sit
on that same throne. Okay. So, let's
take a look at another example of that.
Go to Psalms 132 and read verse 11 and
12.
The Lord has sworn in truth unto David.
He will not turn from it. Of the fruit
of thy body will I sit upon thy throne.
>> And thy children will keep my covenant
and my testimony that I shall teach
them. Their children shall also sit upon
thy throne forever more.
>> Yeah, there it is. If you keep the
Lord's covenant and you overcome, you
going to sit on the same throne Jesus
sitting on, which is the same throne
David going to be sitting on. Okay. Uh
so you had another question. Uh,
can you read that other I think it was
talking about Luke 1:32.
>> Uh, that's the question again. Is Jesus
going to reign on David's throne or is
David going to reign? And he gave uh or
she gave Luke 1 verse 32 and Ezekiel 37
24 and 25. Okay, let's go read those
verses. You know, I should have read
them earlier, but let's go read Luke 1
and32.
>> Yep.
>> When you get it, go ahead and read.
>> He shall be great. Shall be called the
Son of the Highest, and the Lord God
shall give unto him the throne of his
father, David.
>> Yeah. And it's talking about Jesus.
God the Father going to give unto him
the throne of his father according to
the flesh.
um David's throne. And then you just
read everybody that keep the covenant of
the Lord, they gonna sit on that same
throne. Okay? Including David. Okay? Um
now Ezekiel 37
verse 24 and 25.
>> And David my servant shall be king over
them. And they shall and they and they
all shall have one shepherd. They shall
also walk in my judgment and observe my
statutes and do them. And they shall
dwell in the land that I have given unto
Jacob, my servant, wherein your fathers
have dwelt. And they shall dwell
therein, even they and their children
and their children's children forever.
And my servant David shall be their
prince forever.
>> Yeah. So yeah, um David, yeah, he going
to be king over Israel. Okay. But you
got to understand Jesus is the king of
kings,
>> right?
>> Okay. So now let's go and read
Revelations 5.
Establish that the Lord, those that
overcome, make that first resurrection,
they going to be kings and priests.
Okay? And Jesus going to be king over
them. All right? So let's go read
Revelations 5:9 and 10.
And they saw a new song, saying, Thou
are worthy to take the book, and to open
the seal thereof. For thou was slain,
and hast redeemed us to God by thy
blood, out of every kindred and tongue
and people and nation, and hast made us
unto our God kings and priests, and we
shall reign on the earth.
>> Yeah. So, they're gonna reign with the
Lord and sit on David's throne. Okay. I
I I think that's answered the question.
If anybody want to add, they can.
>> All right, brother. I think you hit that
final question of the evening right on
the head, Sister Deborah. Time check.
>> Yes. Uh, could we do just one more for
tonight's question to get into tonight's
This one is very easy to answer.
>> All right, one more. We'll open up to
the Go right ahead.
>> Yes. Okay, we are now into tonight's Q&A
for Wednesday, December the 17, 2025.
And Zion says, "I have ran into plenty
of Hebrew Israelites that say a woman
shouldn't wear pants according to
Deuteronomy 22:5.
Is that true?" And they also want to
know where can you show that you don't
have to wear fringes anymore.
>> All right. Deuteronomy 22. Let's go
there.
>> Verse five.
>> Verse five. And the question is about
women wearing pants. Right.
>> Right.
>> All right. Let's go then. Open that up
to the panel. Deuteronomy 22 and5.
And go ahead, my brother.
>> The woman shall not wear that which
pertainth unto a man, neither shall a
man put on a woman's garment, for all
that do so are abomination unto the Lord
thy God.
>> All right, that uh don't mention nothing
about pants in that verse.
So,
it's all we got on that caller. Go
ahead.
That could be talking about his house
shoes, his shirt. You understand what
I'm saying? His hat,
>> that's too nebulous. They don't say
nothing about pants.
>> And I think as far as about not having
fringes anymore, I think you should re
uh visit that next week so we can put
some time on that.
>> Yes, sir.
>> All right.
>> Okay. So, we'll we'll make that our um
question next week. We'll make that our
number one question. Time check, Sister
Deborah.
>> Yes. The time is 9:05.
>> 9:05. All right. We have ran out of
time. And we'd like to thank everybody
from all around the world who sent in
those questions. And if we didn't have a
chance to get to your question like
we'll do with the fringes, we'll get to
it next week. We also asking all our
viewers from around the world to keep
your questions to a two question maximum
so that we can spread our time evenly
amongst all our viewers. So we want to
thank you all who tuned in with us and
we want to say until we all come
together again, please be safe, be
blessed, stay prayed up and may the Lord
have mercy on us all as brother Tanzel
closes us out. Our Father, which art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name. Thy
kingdom come, thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven. Give us this day our
daily bread, and forgive us of our debts
as we forgive our debtors, and lead us
not into temptation, but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom, and the
power, and the glory forever. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen.